Harry, answer that.
So what do you wanna hack for, Bickle?
I can't sIeep nights.
- There's porno theaters for that. - I know. I tried that.
So what do you do now?
Now? Ride around nights mostly. Subways, buses.
Figure I might as weII get paid for it.
You wanna work uptown? South Bronx, Harlem?
I'II work anytime, anywhere.
Will you work Jewish holidays?
Anytime, anywhere.
Let me see your chauffeur's Iicense.
How's your record? It's cIean.
It's reaI cIean, Iike my conscience.
You gonna break my chops? I got enough troubIe with guys Iike you.
If you're gonna, you can take it on the arches.
Sorry, sir, I didn't mean that.
- PhysicaI? - CIean.
- Age? - 26.
Education?
Some.
Here, there.
Military record?
Honorable discharge.
May 1973.
- Were you in the Army? - Marines.
I was in the Marines too.
So what is it?
You need an extra job?
Are you moonlighting?
Well, I just wanna work long hours.
What's moonlighting?
Look...
...just fill these out and check back tomorrow.
O'Brien, please step up.
Take the car out through 58th Street, please.
Because it's crowded on 57th.
May 10th.
Thank God for the rain, which washed away...
... the garbage and the trash off the sidewalks.
I'm working long hours now.
Six in the afternoon to six in the morning, sometimes even eight.
Six days a week, sometimes seven days a week.
It's a long hustle, but it keeps me real busy.
I can take in $300, $350 a week.
Sometimes even more, when I do it off the meter.
All the animals come out at night.
Whores, skunk-pussies, buggers, queens, fairies, dopers, junkies.
Sick, venal.
Someday, a real rain will come and wash all this scum off the streets.
I go all over. I take people to the Bronx, Brooklyn, Harlem.
I don't care. Don't make no difference to me.
It does to some. Some won't even take spooks.
Don't make no difference to me.
48th and 6th, please.
Man, you are gorgeous! BeautifuI IittIe girI.
I can't afford to get stopped.
We wouldn't want that to happen.
There'II be a big tip for you if you do the right things.
You got a way.
Now you're talking!
Driver, hurry up, will you?
Each night when I return the cab,
I clean the come off the back seat.
Some nights, I clean off the blood.
Can I heIp you?
Yeah, what's your name?
My name is Travis.
That's nice. What can I do for you?
I'd Iike to know what your name is.
Gimme a break.
You can tell me what your name is. I'm not gonna do anything.
- Do you want me to call the manager? - You don't have to--
Troy! AII right. Okay, I mean...
Can I have a ChuckIes there?
Do you have any Jujus? They Iast Ionger. I'd Iike to get them too.
What you see is what we got.
I'II take these.
Coca-Cola.
We don't have Coca-Cola. Royal Crown Cola is all we got.
A dollar eighty-five.
Twelve hours of work and I still can't sleep.
Damn.
Days go on and on. And they don't end.
All my life needed was a sense of someplace to go.
I don't believe that one should devote his life to morbid self-attention.
I believe someone should become a person like other people.
I first saw her at Palantine campaign headquarters at 63rd and Broadway.
She was wearing a white dress.
She appeared like an angel...
... out of this filthy mass.
She is alone.
They...
... cannot...
... touch...
...her.
You delivered two boxes.
I think it's a total of 5000 campaign buttons.
Now, all the ones we had before and our slogan is...
..."We are the people," and "are" is underlined.
These new buttons have "we" underlined.
That reads, " We are the people." Well, I think there's a difference.
"We are the people" is not the same as " We are the people."
Let's not fight.
Look, we'II make it reaI simpIe.
We don't pay for the buttons.
- We throw the buttons away, all right? - Tom, come here a minute.
What?
If Andy okays this canvass report, send a copy to aII headquarters.
I gotta xerox that New York Times articIe.
- Don't forget the new photos. - I didn't.
We have to emphasize mandatory welfare. That's the issue to push.
First push the man, then the issue.
Senator Palantine is a dynamic man.
An intelligent, interesting, fresh, fascinating man.
You forgot sexy.
I did not forget sexy.
You sound Iike you're seIIing mouthwash.
We are selling it.
- Are we authorized to do that? - Very funny.
You can get in trouble selling pharmaceuticals here.
My uncle's in jail because of that.
It's not reaIIy jaiI. Of course, with his wife, anything wouId be jaiI.
Look over there.
I Iove you.
Notice anything?
- No. - Well, put your glasses on.
Okay, just a minute. AII right.
That taxi driver's been staring at us.
What taxi driver?
The one that's sitting there.
- How Iong has he been there? - It feeIs Iike a Iong time.
- Does he bother you? - No.
You mean yes. You're being sarcastic.
You're quick. You're really quick.
I try to be reaI quick.
I'II pIay the maIe in this reIationship--
Good Iuck.
-- and tell him to move. And I don't need good luck.
Oh yes, you do. You just think you don't.
You're blocking our doorway. You think you might move your cab?
You know, eye shadow, mascara...
...Iipstick, rouge.
Not rouge. Blush-on, they call it.
- The kind with the brush. - Yeah, it's Blush-on.
Travis
- Hey, Wiz. - That's Blush- on. My wife uses it.
Ask Travis. He's a Iadies' man.
A cup of coffee.
Whatever the fuck it is, she uses a Iot of it.
And then perfume. The spray kind.
Then in the middle of the Triboro Bridge--
And this woman is beautiful, she changes her pantyhose.
- No. - Oh, yeah.
What'd you do? I throw the man out, and I jump in the back seat and whip it out.
And I said, "You know what this is?"
She says, " It's love." I fuck her brains out.
She goes wild and says,
"That's the greatest single experience of my life."
Then she gave me a $200 tip and her phone number in Acapulco.
You know Doughboy, Charlie T.
Hey, Travis. Got change for a nickeI?
Doughboy will do anything for a buck.
So how's it hanging?
What's that?
I turn on the radio. Some fIeet driver from BeII just got aII cut up.
Stickup?
No, he got cut up by some crazy fucker. Cut half his ear off.
Where? It was on 122nd Street.
Fucking Mau Mau Iand.
You run all over town, don't you, Travis?
Travis
You run all over town, don't you?
You handle some pretty rough customers.
Yeah, I have.
You carry a piece?
You need one?
I know a feIIa who can get you a reaI nice deaI.
Lots of shit around.
I never use mine. I'm conservative.
But it's a good thing to have just as a threat.
I'm gonna go dig my dirt.
Travis
Look.
Piece of ErroI FIynn's bathtub.
Dig the symbols.
F-4-0-5-4-3-4.
And the watermark.
There's one person...
...there's two persons...
...and there's three persons.
I got this at his estate, The Pines.
Take it, and if you can sell it, you give me half of what you got.
I don't want to.
I'm gonna get in my cab and boogie.
Oh, I'm so terribIy sorry.
Nothing. That's very cute. Thank you.
Hey, you wanna see something?
Wait, I just typed, "You wanna see something?"
If you had
these three fingers missing on this hand...
...and that hand missing on that hand...
- ...how would you light the match? - I wouldn't.
Go ahead. Give it a try.
Well, I don't think I could do it.
No?
It's gonna be difficuIt.
I'II give it a try.
I got my thumb back for a second. Thank God.
Just a minute.
I can't do it.
The guy at the newsstand can.
Well, I don't work at a newsstand.
- Anyway, he's probably ltalian. - No.
- You're sure? - He's black.
If he had been ItaIian, he might've been a thief.
If a thief screws up on the job, the mob bIows his fingers off.
This sounds Iike a joke, but it's true.
If they kiII a stooI pigeon, they Ieave a canary on the body.
- It's symboIic. - Why not a pigeon instead of a canary?
I don't know why not. Wait a minute.
You gotta catch a pigeon. A canary, you can walk into a pet store...
...kill it right there. Put it on anyone you want.
- I'd Iike to voIunteer. - I'II take you right over here.
I'd rather voIunteer to her, if you don't mind.
Why do you have to volunteer to me?
Because you are the most beautifuI woman I have ever seen.
Thanks.
But what do you think of Palantine?
I……
The man you're volunteering to help elect President.
I don't know what his poIicies are,
but I'm sure he'II make a good one.
- Do you want to canvass? - Yeah, I'II canvass.
How do you feeI about his stand on weIfare?
I don't reaIIy know his stand on weIfare, but I'm sure it's a good stand.
You're sure of that?
We all work together here, day and night...
...so I'm sure the gentIemen wiII sign you up over there.
The thing is, I drive a taxi at night, so it's kind of hard for me...
...to work in the day.
Then what exactly do you want?
Would you like to have coffee and pie with me?
Why?
Why? I'II teII you why.
I think you're a IoneIy person.
I drive by a Iot, and I see you here.
I see a Iot of peopIe around you...
...and I see these phones and aII this stuff on your desk...
...and it means nothing.
And when I came inside and met you...
...I saw in your eyes and how you carried yourseIf...
...that you're not a happy person.
And I think you need something.
If you wanna caII it a friend, you can caII it that.
You're gonna be my friend?
What do you say?
It's a IittIe hard standing here and asking you, so...
Five minutes, that's all. Just outside. Right around here.
I'm there to protect you.
Come on. Just take a IittIe break.
I have a break at 4:00. If you're here--
4:00 today?
- I'II be here. - I'm sure you wiII.
- AII right. Four p.m. - Right.
- Outside in the front? - Yes.
OK
Oh, my name is Travis. Betsy?
Travis.
I appreciate this, Betsy.
May 26th, four o'clock p.m.
I took Betsy to Charles' Coffee Shop on Columbus Circle.
I had black coffee and apple pie with a slice of melted yellow cheese.
I think that was a good selection.
Betsy had coffee and a fruit salad dish.
She could've had anything she wanted.
15,000 volunteers in New York alone isn't bad.
But the organizationaI probIems!
Yeah, I know what you mean. I got the same probIems.
I gotta get organized. LittIe things, Iike my apartment, my possessions.
I should get a sign: "One of these days, I'll get organiz-ized."
You mean "organized"?
Organiz-ized.
Organiz-ized. It's a joke.
O-R-G-A-N-E-Z-I-E-Z-D.
You mean "organiz-ized." Like those signs in offices that say, "Thimk."
Do you Iike where you work?
We've got some good people. Palantine's got a good chance.
You know you have beautifuI eyes?
Do you Iike the guy you work with?
He's okay.
But do you Iike him?
He's funny and very good at his job. Though he does have a few problems.
I'd say he has quite a few probIems.
His energy seems to go in the wrong places.
When I waIked in and I saw you two sitting there...
...I couId just teII that there was no connection...
...whatsoever.
And when I waIked in, there was something between us.
There was an impulse we were both following.
So that gave me the right to talk to you.
Otherwise, I never wouId've had the right to taIk to you.
I never wouId've had the courage to taIk to you.
And with him, I feIt there was nothing.
When I waIked in, I knew I was right. Did you feeI that way?
I wouIdn't be here if I didn't.
Where are you from?
Upstate.
That fellow, I don't like him.
Not that I don't Iike him, I just think he's siIIy.
I don't think he respects you.
I don't beIieve I've ever met anyone quite Iike you.
You wanna go to...
...a movie with me?
- I have to go back to work now. - I don't mean now. Another time?
Sure. You know what you remind me of?
What? That song...
...by Kris Kristofferson.
Who's that? The songwriter.
" He's a prophet...
He's a prophet and a pusher...
...partly truth, partly fiction, a walking contradiction."
You saying that about me?
Who else would I be talking about?
I'm no pusher. I've never pushed.
Just the part about the contradictions.
You are that.
I called Betsy again. She said maybe we'd go to a movie...
...after work tomorrow. That's my day off.
At first she hesitated, but I called her again and she agreed.
Betsy, Betsy. Oh, no.
Betsy what? I forgot to ask her last name.
Damn! I gotta remember stuff like that.
Don't worry about anyone committing themselves...
...untiI things come in from CaIifornia.
Listen, I think we shouId've waited for the Iimo.
I don't mind the cab, but I mind...
...going to California without the right preparation.
Are you Charles Palantine, the candidate?
Yes, I am.
I teII everybody that
comes in this taxi that they have to vote for you.
Why, thank you...
...Travis.
I'm sure you'II win. Everybody I know wiII vote for you.
I was gonna put your sticker in my taxi...
...but the company said it was against their policy.
They're a bunch of jerks.
Let me tell you, I have learned more about America...
...from riding in cabs than in all the limos in the U.S.
- Oh, yeah? - That's true.
- Can I ask you something, Travis? - Sure.
What bugs you the most about this country?
Well, I don't know. I don't follow political issues that closely, sir.
Well, there must be something.
Well, whatever it is, he should clean up this city here...
...because it's Iike an open sewer. It's fuII of fiIth and scum.
Sometimes I can hardIy take it.
Whatever becomes the President should just...
...really clean it up. You know?
Sometimes I go out and I smeII it. I get headaches, it's so bad.
And they just never go away, you know?
I think that the President shouId just...
...clean up this mess. He should flush it right down the fucking toilet.
I think I know what you mean, Travis.
But it's not gonna be easy.
- We'II have to make radicaI changes. - Damn straight.
Here you go. Keep the change.
Thank you.
- Nice talking to you. - Nice talking to you.
You're a good man. I know you're gonna win.
Thank you, I think.
Just get me outta here, all right?
Come on!
Come on, baby. This is a reaI drag.
Now, come on! Don't make a scene.
You wanna get busted?
Bitch, be cooI!
Don't start no trouble.
Cabbie, just forget about this.
Be cool, bitch!
Get your ass out of here!
Hi there.
- Have a nice day today? - Not particularly.
Got a present for you.
Now back to Gene Krupa's syncopated style shortly.
Why'd you do that?
What else am I gonna do with my money?
I wish you'd have Iistened to this.
I wouId have, except my record pIayer doesn't work now.
Your stereo's broken?
How do you stand it? I can't Iive without music.
I don't foIIow music too much, but I wouId reaIIy Iike to.
Then you haven't played this record yet.
No
But I was thinking maybe we couId Iisten to it on your record pIayer.
Now, going back through 40 years of Chick Webb.
You gotta be kidding.
What? This is a dirty movie.
No, no. This is a movie that a Iot of coupIes come to.
- AII kinds of coupIes go here. - You sure about that?
Yeah, I see them aII the time.
Come on.
- Where are you going? - I have to Ieave.
- Why? - I don't know why I came in here.
- I don't Iike these movies. - WeII, I mean--
I didn't know you'd feeI that way about this movie.
- If I had-- - Are these the onIy movies you go to?
Yeah, I mean I come and-- This is not so bad.
Taking me here is as exciting to me as saying, " Let's fuck."
There are other movies I can take you to.
I don't know much about them, but I can take you other pIaces.
We're just different.
- Wait a second. - I have to go.
I've got to go now.
- Wait a second, I want to taIk. - But I have to go.
Taxi!
Can I taIk to you at Ieast? Won't you at Ieast to taIk to me?
Take the record.
- I've aIready got it. - But, pIease.
- I bought it for you, Betsy. - Okay, now I've got two. Let's go.
Can I caII you?
Jesus Christ, I got a taxi.
Hello, Betsy.
Hi, it's Travis.
Listen, I'm sorry about the other night.
I didn't know that was the way you feIt about it.
Well, I didn't know. If I-- I'd have taken you somewhere else.
Are you feeling better or...?
Maybe you had a virus or something. A 24-hour virus, you know.
It can happen. Yeah.
You've been working hard, huh?
Would you like to have some dinner with me...
...in the next few days or something?
How about a cup of coffee?
I couId come by the headquarters or something, and we couId...
Okay, okay.
Did you get my flowers and the...?
You didn't get them? But I sent some fIowers.
OK
Can I caII you again?
Tomorrow or the next day?
No, I'm gonna-- Okay, yeah, sure.
So Iong.
I tried several times to call her...
...but after the first call, she wouldn't come to the phone.
I also sent flowers, but with no luck.
The smell of the flowers made me sicker.
The headaches got worse. I think I got stomach cancer.
I shouldn't complain, though.
You're only as healthy...
You're only as healthy as you feel.
You're only...
...as healthy...
...as...
...you...
... feel.
- Let's not have trouble. - Why won't you talk to me?
You think I don't know you're here?
You think I don't know?
- Please leave. - Take your hands off!
I just want you to know--
Please. This is no place to do this.
- Take your hands off!
- Take your hands off! - Just Ieave.
- AII right, Ieave, then! - I wanna teII you...
...you're in hell! And you'll die in hell.
- There's a cop over there. - You're Iike the rest of them.
Look, I'm caIIing the cop. Officer!
Officer!
Don't come around here, because I'II caII the poIice!
I realize now, how much she's just like the others, cold and distant.
Many people are like that.
Women for sure. They're like a union.
Yo, cabbie!
Pull over to the curb over there. Right over there.
No, don't.
The fucking meter. What are you doing?
What are you doing with the meter?
Did I teII you to do that with the meter?
Put the meter back.
I don't care what I have to pay.
I'm not getting out. Put the meter back on.
Put it down.
That's right. Put it down!
That's right.
Why are you writing? Don't write!
Put the thing down. Just sit.
I didn't tell you to write. I just said, " Pull over."
Pull over to the curb and sit here.
We're gonna sit.
Cabbie, you see that Iight up there? In the window?
The Iight? The window in the second fIoor.
The one that's closest to the edge of the building.
The Iight up in the window. Second story.
What are you, blind?
Do you see the Iight?
Yeah, you see it. Good.
See the woman?
Do you see the woman in the window?
Yeah.Do you see the woman in the window?
I want you to see that woman because that's my wife.
But that's not my apartment.
It's not my apartment. You know who Iives there?
No, you wouldn't know. But you know who lives there?
A nigger Iives there.
How do you Iike that?
And I'm gonna kiII her.
There's nothing else. I'm gonna kill her.
What do you think of that?
I said, "What do you think of that?"
Don't answer.
You don't have to answer everything.
I'm gonna kiII her with a .44 Magnum pistoI.
I have a .44 Magnum pistoI. I'm gonna kiII her with that gun.
Did you ever see what a .44 Magnum can do to a woman's face?
It'd fucking destroy it. Just bIow it right apart.
That's what it can do to a face.
Did you ever see what it can do to a woman's pussy?
You should see what a .44 Magnum's gonna do to a woman's pussy.
What's that?
I know you must think that I'm, you know...
You must think I'm pretty sick or something.
Right? You must think I'm pretty sick?
Right? I bet you reaIIy think I'm sick, right?
You think I'm sick?
You don't have to answer. I'm paying for the ride.
I picked up this midget, you know.
He's very well-dressed, ltalian suit...
...good-Iooking, with a beautifuI bIonde.
- A Iady midget? - No, the guy was a midget.
- The blonde was a lady. - I got you.
Those midgets are funny.
Sometimes I Iike to hoId a midget.
They always want to sit in the front seat.
Then I pick up these two fags. They're going downtown.
They're wearing rhinestone T-shirts. They start arguing and yelling.
The other one says, "You bitch," and starts beating him.
I say, " I don't care what you do in the privacy...
...of your own home, behind closed doors."
This is a free country.
We got a pursuit of happiness thing. You're consenting, you're adult.
But, you know, in my fucking cab, don't go busting heads.
- Do what you want. - Tell them to go to California.
In CaIifornia, when two fags spIit up, one's got to pay the other aIimony.
Not bad. They're way ahead out there, you know? California.
So I teII them to get out.
One time, I saw a cop chase this guy with one Ieg.
- He was on crutches, you know. - The cop?
No, the dude he was chasing. Fucking cops, they chase anything.
You got that five you owe me?
My man is Ioading, Ioading.
I be broke if I hadn't caught me some peopIe from Ohio out at Kennedy.
I took them into Manhattan by way of Long Beach, tipped me $5.
How's the action around?
It's very sIow.
I'm shoving on.
Hey, Wiz, wait.
- Can I taIk to you for a second? - Bye, KiIIer.
Thank you
You can have them!
Hey, don't be hitting my man!
You better take your ass out, boy!
Yeah
I know you and I ain't taIked too much, you know.
But you've been around, so...
Shoot, that's why they call me the Wizard.
I got...
It's just that I got a...
Things got you down?
Yeah, happens to the best of them.
Yeah, they got me reaI down. ReaI...
I just want to go out...
...and you know, really, really do something.
Taxi Iife, you mean?
Yeah
No, it's...
I don't know.
I just want to go out...
I reaIIy
I reaIIy want to...
I got some bad ideas in my head.
Look at it this way.
A man takes a job.
And that job...
...you know, that becomes what he is.
You know, Iike...
You do a thing, and that's what you are.
I've been a cabbie for 17 years. Ten years at night.
And I stiII don't own my own cab. You know why?
Because I don't want to. That must be what I want.
To be on the night shift, driving somebody else's cab.
You understand?
You get a job, you become the job.
One guy Iives in BrookIyn, one guy Iives in Sutton PIace.
You get a Iawyer, another guy's a doctor.
Another guy dies, another guy gets well...
...and people are born.
I envy you, your youth.
Go out and get Iaid. Get drunk. Do anything.
You got no choice, anyway. I mean, we're aII fucked.
More or Iess, you know?
I don't know. That's about the dumbest thing I ever heard of.
It's not Bertrand RusseII, but what do you want? I'm a cabbie.
What did I know
I don't even know what you're taIking about.
Maybe I don't know either.
Don't worry so much. Relax, kid, you're gonna be all right.
I know. I've seen a Iot of peopIe...
...and I know.
Okay. Thanks, man.
I guess
Yeah, you know. You're all right.
What do you think of your opponent's chances in the upcoming primary?
Mr. Goodman is a fine man.
I would certainly, if it came to it, prefer him...
... to our opponent in the other party.
I think that my programs are better defined than his.
They're more imaginative. I have a better chance of winning.
It's academic, though. He's not going to win. I am.
I see.
Well, one more thing I'd like to ask you.
How do you feel your campaign is going?
When we came up with our slogan "We are the people"...
... when I said "Let the people rule"...
...I felt I was being overly optimistic.
I must tell you that I am more optimistic now than ever before.
The people are rising to the demands that I have made on them.
The people are beginning to rule.
I feel it is a groundswell. I know...
... it will continue through the primary and in Miami.
And I know it will rise...
... to an unprecedented swell in November.
That bitch! I'II bIow her brains out!
I'II kiII her, goddamn it! I'm gonna get my hands and kiII her!
Shoot, goddamn it!
Hey, Sport.
- That guy keeps following us. - Don't look at him.
Hey, guys.
Wanna take a walk?
Loneliness has followed me my whole life, everywhere.
In bars, in cars...
...sidewalks, stores, everywhere.
There's no escape.
I'm God's lonely man.
June 8th.
My life has taken another turn again.
The days move along with regularity, over and over...
... one day indistinguishable from the next.
A long, continuous chain.
And then suddenly...
... there is change.
This here's Easy Andy. He's a traveling salesman.
How are you doing, Travis?
- You got a .44 Magnum? - It's an expensive weapon.
It's aII right. I got money.
It's a reaI monster.
Stop a car at 100 yards, put a round right through the engine.
Here you go.
It's a premium, high resaIe weapon.
Look at that.
That's a beauty.
I couId seII this gun to some jungIe bunny in HarIem for $500.
But I just deaI high-quaIity goods to the right peopIe.
How about that?
This might be too big for practicaI purposes.
In which case, for you, I'd recommend...
...38 snub-nosed.
Look at this.
That's a beautifuI IittIe gun.
It's nickeI-pIated, snub-nosed,
but basicaIIy a service revoIver.
It'II stop anything that moves.
The Magnum, they use that in Africa for killing elephants.
That .38... ...that's a funny gun.
Some of these guns are Iike toys.
That .38, you go out and hammer nails with it all day...
...come back and it'II cut dead center on target every time.
It's got a reaIIy nice action to it and a heck of a waIIop.
You interested in an automatic?
It's a CoIt .25 automatic. It's a nice IittIe gun.
It's a beautifuI gun.
Holds six shots in the clip, one in the chamber.
If you're dumb enough to put one there.
Here. Look at this.
.380 Walther.
Holds eight shots in the clip.
That's a nice gun.
That's a beautifuI IittIe gun. Look at that.
During World War ll, they used this gun to replace the P 38.
Just given out to officers.
Ain't that a IittIe honey?
- How much for everything? - AII together?
Only a jackass would carry that cannon in the streets like that.
Here's a beautifuI handmade hoIster I had made in Mexico.
Forty dollars.
Three-fifty for the Magnum, two-fifty for the .38...
...one and a quarter for the .25, one- fifty for the .380.
Take this and wait here. I'II waIk down with you.
How about dope? Grass? Hash? Coke?
Mescaline? Downers? Nebutal? Chloral hydrates?
- Uppers, amphetamines? - I'm not interested in that stuff.
I can get you crystaI meth, nitrous oxide.
How about a Cadillac? A brand-new Cadillac...
...with the pink slip, two grand.
June 29th.
I gotta get in shape. Too much sitting has ruined my body.
Too much abuse has gone on for too long.
From now on, it'll be 50 pushups each morning.
Fifty pull-ups. There will be no more pills.
There will be no more bad food, no more destroyers of my body.
It'll be total organization. Every muscle must be tight.
Look at the size of that. Oh, yeah.
Oh, it looks so good.
It's getting harder and harder, and it's throbbing now.
The idea had been growing in my brain for some time.
True force.
All the king's men cannot put it back together again.
- Where do we get more? - Where do you think? At headquarters.
AII the way back there?
- Come on. - They'II work.
- Maybe it's the speakers. - I've done this 100 times.
- You've done this before? - Yes, don't worry.
- When was the Iast time? - I've never done this before.
Betsy
What?
Come here, come here.
Hey
You're a Secret Service man, aren't you?
Just waiting for the senator.
You're waiting for the senator?
That's a very good answer.
Shit, man.
I'm waiting for the sun to shine.
No, the reason I asked if you were a Secret Service man--
I won't say anything--
Is because I--
I saw some suspicious-Iooking peopIe over there.
- You did? - They were right over there.
They were just here.
They were very, very...
Suspicious.
Where did they go?
Is it hard to get to be in the Secret Service?
Why?
I was just curious, because I think I'd be good at it.
I'm very observant.
I was in the Marine Corps, you know.
I'm good with crowds.
I noticed your IittIe pin there. It's Iike a signaI, isn't it?
Sort of.
A signaI. A secret signaI for the Secret Service.
What kind of guns you guys carry?
.38s? .45s? .357 Magnums? Something bigger, maybe?
Look, if you're really interested, if you give me your name and address...
...we'II send you aII the information on how to appIy. How's that?
- You will? - Sure.
OK
Why not?
My name is Henry...
...Krinkle. K-R-I-N-K-L-E.
154 Hopper Avenue.
Hopper?
You know, Iike a rabbit? Hip, hop.
Fair Lawn, New Jersey.
Is there a zip code?
6-1- 0-4-5-2.
That's six digits. 6, 1...
Oh, well, 6-1- 0-4-5.
OK
I was thinking of my teIephone number.
Well, I've got it all.
Henry, we'II get aII the stuff right out to you.
Thanks a Iot. Hey, great. Thanks a Iot. HeII. Jesus.
- Be carefuI today. - Right. WiII do.
You have to be carefuI around a pIace Iike this. Bye.
Damed
Yeah
Faster than you. Fucking sick.
I saw you coming, you fuck.
ShitheeI!
I'm standing here. You make the move.
You make the move.
It's your move.
Don't try it, you fuck.
You talking to me?
Then who the hell else are you talking to? You talking to me?
Well, I'm the only one here.
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to?
Oh, yeah?
OK
Listen, you fuckers, you screwheads.
Here is a man who would not take it anymore.
Who would not let--
Listen, you fuckers, you screwheads.
Here is a man who would not take it anymore.
Who stood up against the scum...
... the cunts, the dogs, the filth, the shit.
Here is someone who stood up.
Here is...
You're dead.
Hey, Travis, qu?pasa?
Hi, Melio. Qu?pasa?
Yeah, man?
Shut your fucking mouth and give me the cash out the drawer. Come on!
- Let's go. Give me the damn cash. - Don't shoot.
Stop taking so Iong. Come on!
Let me have it. Give me the bread.
- This all you got? - That's it.
I don't have any more money, man.
- That's all I got! - You got more.
- I teII you, I got no money! - Reach in your sock.
Give me the rest of the fucking bread.
- Did you get him? - Yeah, I got him.
Shit, man.
- Is he dead? - I don't know. His eyes are moving.
I ain't got a permit. I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Don't worry. I'II take care of it.
Can I pay you? Just get out of here.
No, man. I'II take care of it. Go ahead.
That's the fifth motherfucker this year!
Walt Whitman, that great American poet...
...spoke for all of us when he said...
... "I am the man. I suffered.
I was there. " Today I say to you...
... we are the people. We suffered.
We were there.
We, the people, suffered in Vietnam.
We, the people, suffered. We still suffer...
... from unemployment, inflation...
... crime and corruption.
Dear Father and Mother...
...July is the month I remember...
... which brings not only your wedding anniversary...
...but also Father's Day and Mother's birthday.
I'm sorry I can't remember the exact dates...
...but I hope this card will take care of them all.
I'm sorry, again, I cannot send you my address...
... like I promised to last year.
But the sensitive nature of my work for the government
demands utmost secrecy.
I know you will understand.
I am healthy and well and making lots of money.
I've been dating a girl for a few months...
...and I know you'd be proud if you could see her.
Her name is Betsy, but I can tell you no more than that.
Hey, cabbie, you can't park here.
Come on! Come on, let's go! Let's go! Move it!
-- bear the burden of suffering for the few.
No more will we fight the wars of the few...
... through the heart of the many.
I hope this card finds you all well, as it does me.
I hope no one has died. Don't worry about me.
One day there will be a knock on the door and it'll be me.
Love, Travis.
Don't you have some idea?
I'm not the one who wants to talk.
You must know that the reason that I didn't marry him...
... is because I couldn't stand to be a cause of divorce.
Now he's getting a divorce anyway.
Phillip wants to marry me, Brock.
I do love him.
What about us, June?
Our marriage?
You know our marriage wasn't legal.
In the eyes of God, we are married.
Brock, please don't do this to me.
I love him--
Damn.
God damn!
- Are you Iooking for some action? - Yeah.
See that guy over there?
Go talk to him. His name is Matthew.
I'II be over there waiting for you.
Your name Matthew? I want some action.
Officer.
I swear I'm cIean. I'm just waiting here for a friend.
You're gonna bust me for nothing, man?
I'm not a cop. I ain't a--
Then why are you asking me for action?
Because she sent me over.
I suppose that ain't a .38 you got in your sock.
.38?
I'm cIean, man.
Shit, you're a reaI cowboy?
That's nice, man. AII right. That's aII right.
15 dollars, 15 minutes. 25 dollars, half an hour.
Shit.
Cowboy, huh?
I once had a horse. On Coney IsIand.
She got hit by a car.
Well, take it or leave it.
If you wanna save yourseIf some money, don't fuck her.
She'II be back for more.
She's 12 years old. You ain't never had no pussy like that.
Do anything you want. Come on her...
...fuck her in the mouth, in the ass. Come on her face.
She'II get your cock so hard, she'II make it expIode.
But no rough stuff. AII right?
AII right, I'II take it.
Hey, man! Don't take out no money over here.
You gonna fuck me?
You're gonna fuck her. You give her the money.
Catch you Iater, copper.
What'd you say? See you Iater, copper.
I'm no cop, man.
Well, if you are, it's entrapment already.
I'm hip.
Funny, you don't Iook hip.
Have yourself a good time. Go ahead, man.
You're a funny guy.
But Iooks aren't everything.
Go ahead, man. Have a good time.
You're a funny guy.
Hey
The room'II cost you ten bucks.
I'm timing you too.
Come on.
Are you really twelve?
Listen, mister, it's your time. 15 minutes ain't Iong.
When that cigarette burns out, your time is up.
How old are you?
You won't tell me?
What's your name? Easy.
That's not any kind of name. It's easy to remember.
Yeah, but what's your reaI name?
I don't Iike my reaI name.
What's your reaI name?
Iris.
What's wrong? It's a nice name.
That's what you think.
No, don't do that. Don't you remember me?
Remember when you got into a taxi? It was a checkered taxi.
You got in and that guy Matthew came by...
...and he said he wanted to take you away.
He pulled you away.
I don't remember that.
You don't remember?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
We better make it or Sport will get mad.
- How do you wanna make it? - I don't want to. Who's Sport?
That's Matthew. I caII him Sport.
Wanna make it Iike this?
Listen, I...
Can't you understand something?
You came into my cab. You wanted to get out of here.
I must've been stoned.
Why? They drug you? Come off it, man.
What are you doing?
Don't you wanna make it?
I don't wanna make it. I wanna heIp you.
Well, I could help you.
Damn, man!
Goddamn it!
Shit, man. What the hell's the matter with you?
We don't have to make it, mister.
Damn it! Don't you want out of here?
Can you understand why I'm here?
I think I understand.
I tried to get into your cab...
...and now you wanna come and take me away.
Is that it? Yeah, but don't you wanna go?
I can Ieave any time I want. Then what about that one night?
Look, I was stoned.
That's why they stopped me.
When I'm not stoned I got no pIace eIse to go.
So they just...
...protect me from myself.
I don't know.
I don't know. Okay, I tried.
I understand.
And it means something, really.
Well look, can I see you again?
- That's not hard to do. - Not Iike that.
I mean, you know, reguIarIy. This is nothing for a person to do.
How about breakfast tomorrow?
- Tomorrow? - I get up at 1:00.
One o'clock?
Well, I got that thing. I don't know--
Do you want to or not?
Yeah, I want-- Okay, aII right.
- One o'clock. - One o'clock.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Oh, Iris. My name is Travis.
Thanks a Iot, Travis.
So Iong, Iris. See you tomorrow.
Sweet Iris.
This is yours.
Spend it right.
Come back anytime, cowboy.
I wiII.
Why do you want me to go back to my parents?
They hate me.
Why do you think I spIit? There ain't nothing there.
But you can't Iive Iike this. It's a heII.
A girI shouId Iive at home.
Didn't you ever hear of women's Iib?
What do you mean, "women's lib"?
You're a young girI. You shouId be at home now.
You should be dressed up, going out with boys.
You should be going to school.
- You know, that kind of stuff. - Oh, God, are you square.
I'm not square. You're square.
You're full of shit, man.
What do you mean? You walk out with...
...fucking creeps, IowIifes and degenerates...
...and you sell your little pussy for nothing, man?
For some Iow-Iife pimp?
Stands in a hall.
I'm square? You're the one that's square, man.
I don't go screw and fuck with kiIIers and junkies Iike you.
You call that being hip?
What world you from?
Who's a killer? That guy Sport's a killer.
Sport never killed nobody.
- He killed-- - He's a Libra.
He's a what?
I'm a Libra too. That's why we get aIong so weII.
He Iooks Iike a kiIIer to me.
I think that Cancers make the best Iovers...
...but my whole family's air signs.
He's also a dope-shooter.
What makes you so high and mighty? Will you tell me that?
Don't you ever Iook at your own eyebaIIs in the mirror?
What'II you do about Sport and that oId guy?
- When? - When you Ieave.
I'II just Ieave them.
- Just Ieave? - They got other girIs.
You can't just do that. What are you gonna do?
Want me to call the cops?
The cops don't do nothing. You know that.
Sport never treated me bad. He didn't beat me up once.
But you can't allow him to do the same to other girls.
You can't allow him to do that.
He's the Iowest kind of person.
Somebody's got to do something to him.
He's the scum of the earth.
He's the worst...
...sucking scum I have ever, ever seen.
You know what he told me about you?
He called you names. He called you a little piece of chicken.
He doesn't mean it.
I'II move up to one of them communes in Vermont.
I never seen a commune before, but I don't know...
I saw...
...some photos once in a magazine. It didn't Iook very cIean.
Why don't you come with me?
What? Come to the commune with you? No, no.
Why not?
I don't go to pIaces Iike that. Come on, why not?
I don't get aIong with peopIe Iike that.
Are you a Scorpion?
That's it. You're a Scorpion. I can teII every time.
Besides, I gotta stay here.
Come on. Why? I got something important to do.
So what's so important?
Doing something for the government.
The cab thing is just part-time.
Are you a narc?
Do I Iook Iike a narc?
Yeah
I am a narc.
God! I don't know who's weirder, you or me.
- Sure you don't wanna come with me? - I'II give you the money to go.
- You don't have to. - I want you to take it.
I don't want you to take anything from them.
And I wanna do it.
I don't have anything better to do with my money.
I might be going away for a whiIe.
You're just a IittIe tense, that's aII.
I don't Iike what I'm doing, Sport.
Baby, I never wanted you to Iike what you're doing.
If you ever Iiked what you were doing, you wouIdn't be my woman.
You never spend any time with me anymore.
Well, I got to attend to business, baby.
You miss your man, don't you?
I don't Iike to be away from you either.
You know how I feeI about you.
I depend on you.
I'd be Iost without you.
Don't you ever forget that.
How much I need you.
Come to me, baby.
Let me hold you.
When you're close to me like this, I feel so good.
I onIy wish every man couId know what it's Iike to be Ioved by you.
That every woman, everywhere...
...had a man who Ioves her Iike I Iove you.
God, it's good so close.
You know, at times Iike this...
...I know I'm a Iucky man.
Touching a woman who wants me and needs me.
It's onIy you that keeps me together.
Now I see it clearly. My whole life is pointed...
... in one direction. I see that now.
There never has been any choice for me.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...the next president of the U.S., Senator Charles Palantine.
Thank you, Tom.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...we are met today at a crossroads, Columbus Circle.
This is no ordinary place.
It is a pIace where many roads and many Iives intersect.
It is appropriate that we meet here today...
...because these are not ordinary times.
We meet at a crossroads in history.
For far too Iong, the wrong roads have been taken.
The wrong roads have Ied us into war, into poverty...
...into unemployment and inflation.
Today I say to you, we have reached the turning point.
No Ionger wiII we, the peopIe, suffer for the few.
I wouId Iie to you if I toId you the new roads wouId be easy.
They will not be easy.
Nothing that is right and good has ever been easy.
We, the people, know that.
And we, the people, know the right roads and the good.
Today I say to you, we are the peopIe, you and I.
And it is time to Iet the peopIe ruIe!
Thank you.
AII right, Iet him through. PuII back.
Palantine
Thank you
Over there. Get that man.
Give him some air!
Give him some air, will you?
- I never saw him. - I saw him run.
- I saw him. - Where was he?
What's happening?
Got the money?
Iris in her room?
OK
Hey, Sport, how you doing?
Okay, okay, my man. How--
- Where do I know you from, man? - I don't know.
How's everything in the pimp business?
Do I know you? No.
Do I know you?
Get out of here. Get Iost.
How's Iris?
You know Iris.
No, I don't know nobody named Iris.
Iris? Come on, get out of here, man.
You don't know Iris? I don't know nobody named Iris.
No?
Get back to your tribe before you get hurt.
I don't want no troubIe, okay?
You got a gun?
Get the fuck out of here, man. Get out of here.
Suck on this.
Hey
You crazy son of a bitch!
Fucking son of a bitch!
I'II kiII you!
I'II kiII you! I'II kiII you! I'II fucking kiII you!
Son of a bitch! I'II kiII you!
Son of a bitch!
You fucking bastard! I'II kiII you!
You crazy son of a bitch! I'II kiII you!
I'II kiII you!
Stop
Don't shoot him!
Dear Mr. Bickle.
I can't say how happy Mrs. Steensma and I were...
... to hear that you are well and recuperating.
We tried to visit you at the hospital...
... when we were in New York to pick up Iris...
...but you were still in a coma.
There is no way we can repay you...
... for returning our Iris to us.
We thought we had lost her...
...and now our lives are full again.
Needless to say...
...you are something of a hero around this household.
I'm sure you want to know about Iris.
She's back in school and working hard.
The transition has been very hard for her...
...as you can well imagine.
But we have taken steps to see...
...she has never cause to run away again.
In conclusion...
...Mrs. Steensma and I would like to again thank you...
... from the bottom of our hearts.
Unfortunately, we cannot afford to come to New York again...
... to thank you in person, or we surely would.
But if you should ever come to Pittsburgh...
...you would find yourself a most welcome guest in our home.
Our deepest thanks, Burt and Ivy Steensma.
Eddie, the owner-operator, comes up and says, " I want to swap tires."
I say, "These are new tires.
Why not throw in something else, like your wife?"
She was Miss New Jersey, 1957. That's why the fleet has no spares.
Doughboy, Wizard, Killer.
- Charlie T. - What's happening?
Hey, Travis, you got a fare.
Shit.
Well, see you later.
See you, Travis.
Hello, Travis.
Hello.
I hear PaIantine got the nomination.
Yeah, won't be Iong now. Seventeen days.
Well, I hope he wins.
I read about you in the papers. How are you?
It was nothing, reaIIy. I got over that.
Papers always blow these things up.
Just a IittIe stiffness. That's aII.
Travis...
I'm...
How much was it?
So Iong.